bunkblog.net 2014-06-25

# Privacy Policy • BunkBlog

Your privacy is important to BunkBlog. This privacy statement provides information about the personal information that BunkBlog collects, and the ways in which BunkBlog uses that personal information.

###  **Credit**

This document was created using a Contractology template available at [http://www.freenetlaw.com](http://www.freenetlaw.com/).

 **Personal information collection**

BunkBlog may collect and use the following kinds of personal information:

l  [information about your use of this website;]

l  [information that you provide using for the purpose of registering with the website;]

l  [information about transactions carried out over this website;]

l  [information that you provide for the purpose of subscribing to the website services; and]

l  [any other information that you send to BunkBlog.]

 **Using personal information**

BunkBlog may use your personal information to:

l  [administer this website;]

l  [personalize the website for you;]

l  [enable your access to and use of the website services;]

l  [publish information about you on the website;]

l  [send to you products that you purchase;]

l  [supply to you services that you purchase;]

l  [send to you statements and invoices;]

l  [collect payments from you; and]

l  [send you marketing communications.]

Where BunkBlog discloses your personal information to its agents or sub-contractors for these purposes, the agent or sub-contractor in question will be obligated to use that personal information in accordance with the terms of this privacy statement.

In addition to the disclosures reasonably necessary for the purposes identified elsewhere above, BunkBlog may disclose your personal information to the extent that it is required to do so by law, in connection with any legal proceedings or prospective legal proceedings, and in order to establish, exercise or defend its legal rights.

###  **Securing your data**

BunkBlog will take reasonable technical and organisational precautions to prevent the loss, misuse or alteration of your personal information.

BunkBlog will store all the personal information you provide [on its secure servers].

[Information relating to electronic transactions entered into via this website will be  protected by encryption technology.] ** **

###  **Cross-border data transfers**

Information that BunkBlog collects may be stored and processed in and transferred between any of the countries in which BunkBlog operates to enable the use of the information in accordance with this privacy policy.

[In addition, personal information that you submit for publication on the website will be published on the internet and may be available around the world.]

You agree to such cross-border transfers of personal information.

###  **Updating this statement**

BunkBlog may update this privacy policy by posting a new version on this website.

You should check this page occasionally to ensure you are familiar with any changes.

###  **Other websites**

This website contains links to other websites.

BunkBlog is not responsible for the privacy policies or practices of any third party.

Articles written on BunkBlog may contain information and images from a variety of sources. Sometimes as we search pictures and information on a search engine, it is impossible to find out who to credit. If you believe something belongs to you, please [contact us](http://bunkblog.net/contact-2 "Contact") and we will be glad to credit you.

All pictures and commentary of Bunk The Pug are the property of this website. Please credit us if you plan on using it.
